{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Heat Pump Repair Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40287/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40287,"taskName":"Heat Pump - Repair or Service","taskDescription":"Repair or Service a Heat Pump","xmTaskDescriptor":"Heat Pump Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":117,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"HVAC Heat Pump conditioning condition","textMessagingName":"Svc Heat Pump","rolloverLongDesc":"Uses the same technology as an air conditioner. Cools in summer \u0026 heats in winter. Has a unit that looks like the outside part of an air conditioner. Not as powerful a heater as gas forced air, but very energy efficient. Regular servicing necessary for good performance.","rolloverShortDesc":"Heats \u0026 cools. Has outside unit like air conditioner.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Service a Heat Pump.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Heat Pump Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix a Heat Pump","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":39,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Heat Pump Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Heat Pump - Repair or Service","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Heat Pump Project","urlName":"Heat-Pump-Repair-or-Service","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Heat Pump Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"heat pump, geothermal heat pump, hvac, heating, cooling","emcCategoryOid":-12040,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":588,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40287/":{"taskOID":40287,"originalTaskOID":40287,"setID":588,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4723,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which of the following problems need repaired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4304,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Nothing happens when it is turned on","answerDisplayText":"Nothing happens when it is turned on","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1974,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Doesn't get warm enough","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't get warm enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Runs constantly","answerDisplayText":"Runs constantly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1066,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Blows cold air instead of warm","answerDisplayText":"Blows cold air instead of warm","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10096,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4722,"questionDisplayText":"Heat pump type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of heat pump is it?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":723,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Air-source heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Air-source heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2870,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ground-source heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Ground-source heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6911,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Water-source heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Water-source heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4724,"questionDisplayText":"Equipment Age","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is the heating equipment?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10097,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10098,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10099,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"11 - 15 years","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10100,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"16 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10101,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4723,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which of the following problems need repaired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4304,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Nothing happens when it is turned on","answerDisplayText":"Nothing happens when it is turned on","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1974,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Doesn't get warm enough","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't get warm enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Runs constantly","answerDisplayText":"Runs constantly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1066,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Blows cold air instead of warm","answerDisplayText":"Blows cold air instead of warm","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10096,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4304,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Nothing happens when it is turned on","answerDisplayText":"Nothing happens when it is turned on","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1974,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Doesn't get warm enough","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't get warm enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Runs constantly","answerDisplayText":"Runs constantly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1066,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Blows cold air instead of warm","answerDisplayText":"Blows cold air instead of warm","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10096,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4722,"questionDisplayText":"Heat pump type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of heat pump is it?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":723,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Air-source heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Air-source heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2870,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ground-source heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Ground-source heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6911,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Water-source heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Water-source heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":723,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Air-source heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Air-source heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2870,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ground-source heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Ground-source heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6911,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Water-source heat pump","answerDisplayText":"Water-source heat pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4724,"questionDisplayText":"Equipment Age","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is the heating equipment?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10097,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10098,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10099,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"11 - 15 years","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10100,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"16 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10101,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10097,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"Less than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10098,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 10 years","answerDisplayText":"5 - 10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10099,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"11 - 15 years","answerDisplayText":"11 - 15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10100,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16 - 20 years","answerDisplayText":"16 - 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10101,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 20 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}